{
    "id": "68270bb14c8e49368e9de9f53f8d99f7",
    "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The summer term ………………….. on April 18th.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is starting",
                "starts"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0be4d16cbd6e46d7b62823857fedcad1"
        },
        {
            "question": "My plane ………………. at",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leaves",
                "is leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "197f008e5c1d4662aa21c3776caf99cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "When …………………. in Bangkok?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is the train arriving",
                "does the train arrive"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d8432ad0f5fc4498ac50498c36e18386"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will pay you back when I ………………….. a job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will get",
                "get",
                "am getting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "874485a732114e728a3a03a58e63bbb4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… to the US next week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "am going"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db51f7c125294c60abaf4d9b7c477bc0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. for a new job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "looks",
                "is looking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4713ccecd9274a6a9f1e95762a1f449b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Granny’s train ………………….. at",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "arrives",
                "is arriving"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a0042397f394587b8c58236a9b9a333"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will tell you if I ………………….. her name.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knew",
                "will know"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0cef28e33a8e48fbbe31f4bbf865fa81"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘What ………………… there?’ ‘I …………………. a cake.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do you do make",
                "are you doing am making"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d9bf8ca96ed34b069112421b9c14f551"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. Lucia on Tuesday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "am seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3142de600c7045579ee6b4ae3090428b"
        }
    ]
}